{
  "posts": [
    {
      "id": "hello",
      "date": "2026-02-24",
      "question": "Hello?",
      "answer": "Hi there! ðŸ‘‹\n\nHow can I help you today?",
      "intro": true
    },
    {
      "id": "is-this-real",
      "date": "2026-02-24",
      "question": "Wait, this is real?",
      "answer": "**You're absolutely right!** briantemple.ai is a 86 billion neuron model available to answer any of your questions. What's on your mind?",
      "intro": true
    },
    {
      "id": "about",
      "date": "2026-02-24",
      "question": "Who are you?",
      "answer": "Hi, [I'm Brian](https://www.briantemple.com). It's nice to meet you.",
      "intro": true
    },
    {
      "id": "hi",
      "date": "2026-02-25",
      "question": "Hi",
      "answer": "Hi! ðŸ‘‹"
    },
    {
      "id": "ai-jobs",
      "date": "2026-02-25",
      "question": "Is AI going to take my job?",
      "answer": "You don't have to worry about me. Pinky promise."
    },
    {
       "id": "taxes",
       "date": "2026-02-25",
       "question": "Can you help me with my taxes?",
       "answer": "Absolutely not."
     },
     {
       "id": "lucky",
       "date": "2026-02-26",
       "question": "Lucky numbers?",
       "answer": "I find \"The Luckiest Guy on the Lower East Side\" by The Magnetic Fields to be a pretty catchy number."
     },
     {
       "id": "wassup",
       "date": "2026-02-26",
       "question": "Yo duuuude wasssssupp",
       "answer": "Dude! :)"
     },
     {
        "id": "brian",
        "date": "2026-02-26",
        "question": "Are you Brian Temple?",
        "answer": "On good days."
      },
      {
         "id": "beans",
         "date": "2026-02-26",
         "question": "Can I have beans with every meal?",
         "answer": "I believe in you."
      },
      {
         "id": "respond",
         "date": "2026-02-27",
         "question": "Will you ever respond to my questions??",
         "answer": "Loading..."
      }
  ]
}
